[

](https://yapiapp.com/)

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is important to us. Please read and familiarize yourself with our company’s Privacy Policy. This policy will inform you on the types of information we collect from our website visitors.

**Effective Date: August 1, 2020** 

Yapi Inc. and Yapiapp.com
-------------------------

Yapi Inc., and yapiapp.com (“Yapi,” “we,” “us”) are committed to protecting your privacy.

This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected from our site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to ensure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Please Note:**The privacy practices outlined in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you link to other websites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

### **Information We Collect About You and How It’s Collected** 

**Information You Provide To Us** 

Any information we collect on or through our Website may include any of the following:

**Account Set-Up**

If you set up an account to receive services, we will collect your name, phone number, email address, and account settings to process your registration and provide those services.

**Sales Orders, Product Registration, and Customer Support**

When you order products or services from us, register your product, or contact our customer support associates, we will collect your name, email address, address, phone number, and payment-related information, each as applicable, so that we can fulfill your order, register your product, provide the products or services that you have requested, and provide information about product or service offerings that might interest you.

**Feedback and Postings**

When you provide us feedback, post information on our forums, or send us correspondence, we may collect the information you submit to address the business purpose of your communication.

**Web Form Submissions** 

When you provide any information via a web form on our site, which asks for information such as your email, phone number, and other identifiable information. This also includes information provided at the time of subscribing to our services, managing your subscription to our services, and requesting further information or a demonstration of our product. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website, Application, or our services.

**Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies**

Through the use of third-party partners, our website uses advanced data and tracking technologies to gather useful information on all of our website visitors. This information helps us to make data-driven decisions about our products and services as well as to measure and improve upon the overall experience for each user. Through these tracking technologies, we collect the following information and data:

* Information such as geographic location, the date and time of your website visits, the referring pages you landed on, and the pages you exited from. 
* Information about the devices you visited our site from in addition to your IP Address, the make, and model of your mobile device, the browser you visited from, and unique device and advertising identifiers. 
* Technologies we use to capture this information are browser cookies and website pixels. 

### **How We Use Your Collected Information**

**General** 

Your gathered and collected information is used in the following ways; to provide what you have requested pertaining to any information you submitted on our webforms, to provide you with information about our products and services if you request a product demo, to notify you about any account adjustments or changes if you sign up for any of our goods or services, and any other ways in which we may describe when you provide us with your information

**Distribution of Information**

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. 

If we merge with or are acquired by another company, or sell all or substantially all of our relevant assets, or file for bankruptcy, we may disclose and transfer personal information with the company or asset. We will seek appropriate protection for personal information disclosed or transferred in such transactions consistent with applicable law.

### **Cookie/Tracking Technology**

Our website uses cookie and tracking technology with various third-party partners. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to our site, and understanding how visitors use and interact with our website. 

Cookies from us and our third-party partners provide us with data on how our users interact with our website in addition to partners who help to deliver personalized advertisements. Some cookies may potentially track you on other websites to deliver personalized advertising that may be relevant to you. 

If, for any reason, you wish not to be tracked by our third-party partners, please update your web browser settings to block cookies from our site. Please note that disabling some cookies may result in limited functionality within our website. 

### **Control Over Your Information** 

Once we have gathered your information you have consented to provide, if, for any reason, you wish you withdraw your consent, you have the right and can contact us through the contact information given below. 

Please note, you may exercise your rights and choices about how we collect and use your personal information. Our company always provides an opt-out option through any form of email and marketing communications, if you decide at any given time you no longer wish to receive our communications. 

### **Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents, and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to it. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt-out of further mailings.

### **Children Under the Age of 18** 

Our website and services are not directed at children under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information about children under 18 for marketing purposes. If we learn that a child under 18 has submitted personal information to us without parental consent, we will attempt to delete it as soon as possible. If you are under 18, do not provide us with any information on our website. 

### **Comments and Questions**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, please contact us at Yapi Inc., 4100 W. Alameda Ave. Ste. 362, Burbank, CA 91505.

#### Our products

#### Our integrations

#### Why Yapi

Helping thousands of dentists succeed since 2009

[

](https://www.facebook.com/goyapi)[

](https://www.instagram.com/yapi_app/?hl=en) [

](https://www.linkedin.com/company/yapi)[

](https://www.youtube.com/@yapi_dental)

Copyright © 2009-2024 Yapi Inc. All Rights Reserved.

Yapi™ is a property of Yapi Inc.
